(Stuart:)I don't want to rush you,
(Stuart:)but I'm closing
a little early tonight.
(Raj:)Ooh. Hot date?
(Stuart:)Uh, no. I overheard
Bernadette tell Howard
(Stuart:)she was making him a meat loaf,
(Stuart:)and you don't have
to not ask me twice.
If I stick a lightbulb on this,
wouldn't it make a great lamp
(Emily:)for my bedroom?
(Raj:)You're kidding, right?
(Emily:)Oh. Is this freaking you out?
(Raj:)I guess I'm just more
of a Pottery Barn,
(Raj:)Crate and Barrel kind of guy.
(Raj:)Maybe Pier 1
if I really want to cut loose.
(Emily:)All right. Never mind.
(Raj:)No, no, no.
Hey, you should totally get it.
(Raj:)In fact, I'll buy it for you.
Sold!
(Emily:)Raj, you don't have to do that.
Too late!
No returns!
(Leonard:)That was really intense.
(Penny:)Well, now we know, next time
we go to the farmers' market,